<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>market on Rhombus Project Wiki</title>
    <link>https://rhombus.io/wiki/tags/market/</link>
    <description>Recent content in market on Rhombus Project Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://rhombus.io/wiki/tags/market/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Rhombus Open Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://rhombus.io/wiki/tutorial/marketplace/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhombus.io/wiki/tutorial/marketplace/intro/</guid>
      <description>Requirements There are couple of things needed before you can access the Rhombus Open Marketplace:
 Rhombus Desktop client installed &amp;amp; working functional (default) wallet within Rhombus Desktop RHOM coins for buying/selling (get some on available exchanges)  Make sure you have a Rhombus Desktop installed with a working wallet before continuing.
Create Market-enabled wallet To enable the Open Marketplace, you need to create a second wallet and name it Market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ: Rhombus Open Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://rhombus.io/wiki/support/faq/market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhombus.io/wiki/support/faq/market/</guid>
      <description>Are there fees for using the marketplace? Who collects the fees? Do I need to keep my computer online for my listings to stay up? How long do listings stay up? Can I use any other coin other than RHOM? Are regular (fiat) currencies and traditional means of payment accepted? How much privacy does the marketplace offer? Is the marketplace moderated? How does the escrow system functions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Buy/Sell on Open Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://rhombus.io/wiki/tutorial/marketplace/buying-selling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhombus.io/wiki/tutorial/marketplace/buying-selling/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve already installed the Rhombus Open Marketplace and have it enabled on your Rhombus Desktop client, then you&amp;rsquo;re all set and ready to start buying and selling stuff for crypto without giving away your data.
   Complete Buy flow  Listing stage Bidding stage Order stage Escrow stage Escrow stage, pt. II Packaging &amp;amp; shipping stage Delivered/complete stage       Complete Buy flow If you haven&amp;rsquo;t installed or enabled the Rhombus Open Marketplace yet, then follow our Getting started with Rhombus Open Marketplace guide!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
