<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rhombus Wiki on Rhombus Project Wiki</title>
    <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rhombus Wiki on Rhombus Project Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://rhom.com/wiki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Airdrop Details</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-airdrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-airdrop/</guid>
      <description>Airdrop Rhombus coin initial distrubution includes 6 billion RHOM distrubted at a ratio of 500:1 to all BTC addresses with a positive bitcoin balance over 0.001 before BTC block 660023. They are claimable by signing a message from your bitcoin address and submitting to Rhom AirDrop before December 5th, 2021.
 Airdrop API Airdrop Details How To Claim Your Airdrop How To Sign a Message For RHOM  Currently Ongoing Until December 5th, 2021  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICO Detials</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-ico/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-ico/</guid>
      <description>ICO Details Round one currently under until DATE HERE  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Bitcoin codebase</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/bitcoin-codebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/bitcoin-codebase/</guid>
      <description>RHOM is hosted by its own blockchain and is not a token built on another chain (i.e. ERC-20 tokens).
Advantages Being built on the latest Bitcoin codebase not only allows the Rhombus platform to benefit from both Bitcoin’s stability and security, but also enables developers to leverage and easily fork any product, service and technology development from the Bitcoin developer community.
Recent Bitcoin developments implemented in Rhombus include but are not limited to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scalability</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/blockchain-scalability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/blockchain-scalability/</guid>
      <description>Native Segregated Witness (Segwit) Bulletproofs Lightning Network  Instant Payments Scalability Low Cost Cross-Chain       Native Segregated Witness (Segwit) The Rhombus platform was deployed with a native implementation of Segwit.
This has the added benefit of making all transactions (including private ones) go through Segwit by default, resulting in better scalability and cheaper transaction fees.
Unlike forked Segwit implementations, 100% of Rhombus addresses are compatible with Segregated Witness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specifications</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-specifications/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain          Codebase Always up-to-date with latest Bitcoin Core   Consensus mechanism Rhombus Proof-of-Stake (RPoS)   Block time 150 seconds (Quicker then BTC)   Block size 2 MB (2× larger than BTC)    Coin supply          Total &amp;amp; circulating supply between 1-11 billion RHOM (check link for exact number)   ICO Disptrubtion max 200 Million RHOM   Airdrop Distrubution max 10 billion RHOM    Staking          Block reward 100 RHOM   Coin maturity 192 confirmations (~8 hours)   Yearly interest rate 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transaction types</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/privacy/transaction-types/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/privacy/transaction-types/</guid>
      <description>As the highest privacy state requires the most transaction fee, it may not always be the best type of transaction depending on the situation, especially when privacy is not predominantly required by the user.
 Rhombus&amp;#39;s multiple privacy states      Public Blind Anon     Staking      Privacy ∗ ∗∗ ∗∗∗   Hidden TX amount      Anon TX participants      TX fees $ $$ $$$    Why has RHOM different privacy states?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accepting RHOM for Merchants</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/merchants/accepting-rhom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/merchants/accepting-rhom/</guid>
      <description>Advantages Accepting Rhombus (and many other cryptocurrencies) gives you – as a Seller – many advantages over traditional fiat payment systems:
 No chargebacks – all cryptocurrency transactions are final, no chargebacks are possible Complete control – you are the only owner of the private keys to your wallet, no one can freeze your account or shut it down  Online stores Accepting RHOM payments in your online stores is possible with use of Rhombus BTCPayServer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compile &amp; Sign Rhombus Core builds</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/wallets/rhombus-core/compile-sign-builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/wallets/rhombus-core/compile-sign-builds/</guid>
      <description>This guide will walk you through compiling your own Rhombus Core builds via Gitian and optionally signing the builds with your PGP key and uploading the signatures to rhombus/gitian.sigs repository.
The more people would compile their builds and sign them, the better.
If you can spare the time and processing power, please do!     Notes Preparation Compile  Check progress Post-compilation       Notes  This guide is focused on Ubuntu-based distros - on other distributions, you might to install more dependencies etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ: RHOM coin</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/support/faq/rhom-coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/support/faq/rhom-coin/</guid>
      <description>What is RHOM? Where can I buy RHOM coins?  Will RHOM be added to other exchanges?   What is RHOM&amp;rsquo;s codebase? What are the transactions fees for RHOM? What are RHOM&amp;rsquo;s transactions sizes? What is RHOM&amp;rsquo;s inflation rate? Why has RHOM different privacy states? Are whitepapers available for the CT and RingCT privacy protocols? Is Segwit enabled? What are atomic swaps? What is Rhombus&amp;rsquo;s transaction-per-second (TPS) capabilities?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing syncing issues</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/support/syncing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/support/syncing/</guid>
      <description>Rhombus wallets are a network-based software. Make sure that no firewall or anti-virus software is blocking Rhombus from running or connecting the internet. If in doubt, disable them for testing purposes and enable them afterwards if you have identified your problem.
Update to latest version Make sure you&amp;rsquo;re running on latest version.
If not, update your wallet.
Reindex blockchain Relaunch the client with -reindex flag:
Windows  Windows  Rhombus Core: FIXME   macOS  macOS  Rhombus Desktop: launch via /rhombus-desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>This series of guides will walk you through the first steps into Rhombus ecosystem. Buckle up!
Learn about Rhombus This Wiki is a great informational and supportive resource for all things Rhombus. Understanding the whole project might be a bit overwhelming, so we propose studing it piece by piece. Many topics are covered here, but at the bare minimum, you should read all the articles marked with ★ symbol as those are the most important ones:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting your own Coldstaking Pool</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/advanced/hosting-coldstaking-pool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/advanced/hosting-coldstaking-pool/</guid>
      <description>For information about hosting your own coldstaking pool, visit the documentation in the rhombus/coldstakepool repository on GitHub:
VPS Setup Example   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to stake</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/overview/</guid>
      <description>Staking methods Comparison  Standalone staking Cold staking       To learn more in-depth about Rhombus&amp;rsquo;s Staking feature, read Rhombus Staking (intro).
Staking methods You can choose from few options on how to stake:
 Standalone – staking happens directly in your desktop wallet, your PC should be online ideally 24/7 (see below) Staking on a Pool – easily &amp;ldquo;pair&amp;rdquo; your desktop wallet with a Staking Pool; staking will happen automatically on pool Staking on dedicated staking device (DSD) – a fancy way to describe staking on your own SBC like Raspberry Pi or Rock64 without need to rely on third-party pool  Comparison     Standalone Staking pools Dedicated staking devices     Difficulty to setup easiest easy moderate   Staking happens directly in wallet on a pool on dedicated device   Staking type &amp;ldquo;hot&amp;rdquo; staking Cold Staking Cold Staking   Fees – 1–3 % –   Security lower high high   Howto guides – setup guide setup guide    Standalone staking is easiest and fastest way to start staking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposals</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/misc/proposals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/misc/proposals/</guid>
      <description> This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhombus with Tor</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/privacy/tor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/privacy/tor/</guid>
      <description>a) Using the Tor Browser b) Using the Tor Daemon c) Tor as a Hidden Service     The only privacy protocol that’s not enabled by default on Rhombus Desktop is the ability to hide your IP address using the Tor network.
While it could eventually be enabled by default or through the Settings page, Tor currently needs to be activated manually to route your Rhombus Desktop connection through its network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RPC</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/api/rpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/api/rpc/</guid>
      <description> This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running multiple wallets</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/privacy/multiwallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/privacy/multiwallet/</guid>
      <description>Multiwallet setup  Rhombus Core   Autostart multiwallet  Rhombus Desktop Rhombus Core  Linux         You might want to create and use multiple wallets for different usage. The goal is to separate your finances, so they won&amp;rsquo;t mix up. This approach will also help you gain a bit more privacy (never linking all of your available funds).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securely storing Recovery Phrases</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/recovery-phrase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/recovery-phrase/</guid>
      <description>Recovery Phrases (sometimes also called Mnemonic or just Seed) are strings of usually 12, 18 or 24 words, which are used to recover crypto wallets in cases of emergency. That being said, whoever gets access to your Recovery Phrase can access your coins as well. This presents a security risk if your Recovery Phrase gets stolen or discovered by some malicious actor.
Finding the right balance Each security layer used to protect your Recovery Phrase (and optionally Recovery Passphrase) makes it harder for everyone to get access to your coins – that includes both attackers and yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wallets overview</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/wallets/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/wallets/overview/</guid>
      <description>You can use one or all of them, it&amp;rsquo;s up to you.
Overview Rhombus Core is a recommended wallet for most users as it offers the best of Rhombus&amp;rsquo;s features  Desktop Main, desktop wallets for Windows, macOS and Linux
 Rhombus Core – Qt-based wallet focused on stability and advanced features Rhombus Copay – Mobile &amp;amp; desktop wallet with multi-sig for increased security     Mobile Mobile wallets for Android and iOS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup &amp; Restore wallet</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/backup-restore-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/backup-restore-wallet/</guid>
      <description>Your funds are backed up by Recovery Phrase (~ mnemonic seed) during wallet creation and that is enough to keep your coins safe. However if you want to backup all the additional data like addresses saved in Address Book and more, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to backup your wallet.dat file.
Always backup your wallet.dat to a secure place (USB, external drive etc.) – if anyone would get access to it and knew your wallet password, they could steal your coins!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold staking setup</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/cold-staking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/cold-staking/</guid>
      <description>Before we dive into this guide, you might want to familiarize yourself with theory of cold staking, so that you know what we&amp;rsquo;re doing and why.
Rhombus&amp;rsquo;s cold staking setup is quite flexible, meaning there are many options how to stake – each approach has its pros and cons. This guide will outline all the possible variants, so that you can choose your own balance between convenience, privacy and security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connections &amp; peers</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/support/connections/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/support/connections/</guid>
      <description>Clear banned peers  Opening Console in Rhombus Desktop  Open Console:
 Rhombus Desktop: click on the terminal/console icon in bottom left corner Rhombus Core: Help → Debug window → Console tab  Enter clearbanned, press Enter and restart wallet.
Find peers from scratch Delete your peers.dat file in Rhombus directory. This will force the app to find new connections to peers.
Time offset error If you see a time offset error icon, it means that your machine is either ahead of behind a few seconds compared to your peers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to choose a good password</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/good-passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/good-passwords/</guid>
      <description>Trezor wrote a very detailed and in-depth article about choosing strong passphrases for protecting recovery seeds. You can obviously follow this guide to password/passphrase-protect any kind of valuable information (like your Rhombus recovery seed).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhombus Core</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/wallets/rhombus-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/wallets/rhombus-core/</guid>
      <description>Preview of Rhombus Core  Rhombus Core is more lightweight and offers some advanced features like Coin Control
 Download Rhombus Core   Report bugs   Features Browse &amp;amp; compare Rhombus Core&amp;rsquo;s features with other available wallets.
Getting started Installation Please note that even though some of these steps are optional/recommended, it is highly advised to follow all of them as it secures your funds from being lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhombus Insight</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/api/insight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/api/insight/</guid>
      <description>Block Explorer      Example API calls  Blockchain status Latest blocks Block info Transaction info       Example API calls This is a non-exhaustive list of API example usage. See official API docs for complete list.
Blockchain status Get current blockchain data (block height, supply, difficulty(&amp;hellip;)):
https://explorer.rhom.com/rhombus-insight-api/status
{ &amp;#34;info&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;version&amp;#34;: 18010001, &amp;#34;protocolversion&amp;#34;: 90009, &amp;#34;blocks&amp;#34;: 502427, &amp;#34;moneysupply&amp;#34;: 9403349.49981462, &amp;#34;timeoffset&amp;#34;: 0, &amp;#34;connections&amp;#34;: 44, &amp;#34;difficulty&amp;#34;: 957991.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-hosting RHOM payment processor</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/merchants/rhom-payment-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/merchants/rhom-payment-process/</guid>
      <description>By hosting your own instance of Rhombus&amp;rsquo;s BTCPayServer, you can create your very own independent payment processor for both Rhombus and Bitcoin.
   About BTCPayServer Features Available servers Installation  Requirements Generate docker-compose.yml Run BTCPayServer       About BTCPayServer   Features See official BTCPayServer website for complete info about features and abilities. To name a few:
 No fees – no processing/transaction fees or any 3rd-party eating up your profits Peer to peer – coins are sent directly from buyer to seller, they don&amp;rsquo;t sit on the server itself (no middleman) Multiple coins supported – BTC (with optional Lightning), RHOM, LTC and more&amp;hellip; No KYC – keep your identity to yourself Self-hosted – you&amp;rsquo;re in control  Available servers Following BTCPayServer servers are run by the community and open for public, in case you don&amp;rsquo;t want/need to run your own:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Rhombus&#39;s PoS</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/staking/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/staking/intro/</guid>
      <description>About Rhombus Staking Passive Income Cold Staking  Cold Hardware Staking Quantum-resistance &amp;amp; Privacy       About Rhombus Staking Proof-of-Stake (PoS) is a type of algorithm by which a cryptocurrency blockchain network aims to achieve distributed consensus. In PoS-based cryptocurrencies, the creator of the next block is chosen via various combinations of random selection of wealth and age. In contrast, the algorithm of Proof-of-Work (PoW) based cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin rewards participants who solve complicated cryptographical puzzles in order to validate transactions and create new blocks (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chain forks</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/support/fork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/support/fork/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing that Rhombus Core wallet is not syncing any further, then it might be because you got caught on a fork due to the latest hardfork.
If you execute any transaction during this time, it will appear as if you&amp;rsquo;ve lost the coins, but don&amp;rsquo;t worry. Nothing has left your wallet.
Getting on the right chain Getting your client back to a working state requires a bit of work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coingecko</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/api/coingecko/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/api/coingecko/</guid>
      <description>Access CoinGecko data such as live pricing, trading volume, tickers, exchanges, historical data, coin info &amp;amp; images, developer &amp;amp; community stats, events, global markets, and CoinGecko Beam coins &amp;amp; exchanges status updates directly.
 API v3 Docs   Homepage      Example API calls  Get current price Coin&amp;rsquo;s current data Historic data Status updates Global cryptocurrency data   More info     Example API calls This is a non-exhaustive list of API example usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Staking Pools</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/staking/pools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/staking/pools/</guid>
      <description>The importance of decentralization Available Staking Pools Advanced  Running your own Pool        In the context of cryptocurrency mining, a mining pool is the pooling of resources by miners, who share their processing power over a network, to split the reward equally, according to the amount of work they contributed to the probability of finding a block. — Wikipedia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dedicated Staking Devices</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/staking/dedicated-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/staking/dedicated-devices/</guid>
      <description>   This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ledger Wallet</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/wallets/ledger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/wallets/ledger/</guid>
      <description>Ledger Nano S     About Ledger Wallet Requirements Installation  Ledger Rhombus app Rhombus Core configuration   Usage  Sending RHOM using Ledger Cold staking on Ledger       About Ledger Wallet Ledger Nano (S/X) is a hardware wallet which stores user&amp;rsquo;s private keys in a secure hardware device.
Hardware wallets have major advantages over standard software wallets: private keys are stored in a secure chip, and cannot be transferred out of the device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi-signature wallets</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/multisig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/multisig/</guid>
      <description> This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhombus as Tor Hidden Service</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/privacy/tor-hidden-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/privacy/tor-hidden-service/</guid>
      <description>Download Rhombus wallet Install Tor Define HS in Tor config Find your IP for HS Modify rhombus.conf Start wallet     It also protects your machine from geolocation and its possible ugly consequences, and automatically sets you up for both incoming and outgoing connections, helping the Rhombus network. It is recommended to always run the Rhombus through Tor.
This guide is written purely for Linux (specificaly Ubuntu-based distributions).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhombus Copay</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/wallets/rhombus-copay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/wallets/rhombus-copay/</guid>
      <description> This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhomtools staking utility</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/staking/rhomtools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/staking/rhomtools/</guid>
      <description>About Rhomtools Use cases  Advantages   Features     About Rhomtools  Rhomtools displaying staking status  Rhomtools automates all kinds of heavy lifting related to running your own (staking) node. It&amp;rsquo;s very lightweight and runs on many platforms, including ARM (for DSD like Raspberry Pi, Rock64 and others).
As CLI, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer any graphical interface, but it&amp;rsquo;s still very usable and user-friendly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staking on DSD with Rhomtools</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/on-dedicated-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/on-dedicated-device/</guid>
      <description>A Staking Node is a full blockchain node which has been configured to stake on behalf of your wallet (aka it has been delegated staking power over your wallet). The Staking Node is a computer running Rhombus that is always on and always connected to the internet. A Raspberry Pi 3 or comparable device (DSD) makes a perfect staking node as it consumes very little energy, is compact and easy to tailor for dedicated tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips for increasing privacy</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/privacy/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/privacy/tips/</guid>
      <description>Basics Rhombus  Transactions Balances   Network Other resources     Here are a few tips to keep you private as much as possible:
Basics  Never brag about how much RHOM or BTC you own, online or offline. All it does is bringing attention to you; scammers and hackers would surely love to get a piece of your pie. It&amp;rsquo;s not worth the risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airdrop API</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/airdrop/api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/airdrop/api/</guid>
      <description> This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chainz</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/api/chainz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/api/chainz/</guid>
      <description>Services provided by cryptoid.info are free of charge.
Please do not abuse them.   API Docs   Chainz Rhombus Block Explorer      Example API calls  Prices  In BTC In USD   Last 10 TXs Connected nodes RHOM in circulation Block count Rich list   More info     Example API calls Query limit!
Please limit your calls to the Query API to 1 every 10 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coin Control</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/privacy/coin-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/privacy/coin-control/</guid>
      <description> This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold staking on Ledger wallet</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/ledger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/ledger/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial assumes Rhombus has been properly installed on your Ledger Nano S/X hardware device and that your Rhombus Core wallet is set up for Rhombus on Ledger.
Requirements Before starting the setup process, make sure you have:
 Cold staking public key – you can get it by either:  self-hosting a cold staking node (on Raspberri Pi/Rock64 etc.) or by joining one of the available staking pools   A Ledger hardware wallet with Rhombus installed on it Ledger Live app ready to use Rhombus Core wallet installed and fully synced  Staking setup Get your staking public key Staking Pool  Via staking pool Choose one of the available staking pools and note somewhere its staking public key (they are usually right there on the top of the page).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Claim Your Airdrop</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/airdrop/airdrop-claim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/airdrop/airdrop-claim/</guid>
      <description> This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Sign a Message For RHOM</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/airdrop/signing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/airdrop/signing/</guid>
      <description> This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invest</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/ico/invest-ico/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/ico/invest-ico/</guid>
      <description> This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verify integrity of downloads</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/verify-downloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/verify-downloads/</guid>
      <description>About checksums While compiling from source is the recommended and most secure way to build the Rhombus platform, the team realizes this is an advanced technique that a large number of users aren&amp;rsquo;t comfortable with. For most users, each release is distributed with source code and pre-compiled distributions for Windows, Mac &amp;amp; Linux.
To ensure the highest level of security, the Rhombus Project team provides sha256sums for all of these releases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coinmarketcap</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/api/coinmarketcap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/api/coinmarketcap/</guid>
      <description> The world&amp;rsquo;s cryptocurrency data authority has a professional API made for you.
 In contrast to Coingecko API, Coinmarketcap API offers limited free API access and paid premium one.
 API Docs   Homepage   Pricing   Follow official Quickstart docs on how to get started with your developer account and API access.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold staking on Trezor wallet</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/trezor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/trezor/</guid>
      <description> This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ledger wallet</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/wallets/ledger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/dev/wallets/ledger/</guid>
      <description> This article hasn&#39;t been written yet, we&#39;re working on it!  Want to help out? Contribute your articles!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhombus Copay</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/wallets/rhombus-copay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/wallets/rhombus-copay/</guid>
      <description>About Rhombus Copay While it doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer all of available features (compared to other Rhombus wallets) it offers some unique ones.
Mainly, Rhombus Copay is the most accessible mobile Rhombus wallet and allows user-friendly multisignature wallets for increased security of your funds, or even sharing the wallet across multiple people.
 Download for desktop   Report bugs    Preview of Rhombus Copay app on mobile  Features Browse &amp;amp; compare Rhombus Copay&amp;rsquo;s features with other available wallets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhombus CLI</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/wallets/rhombus-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/wallets/rhombus-cli/</guid>
      <description>About Rhombus CLI Features Getting started  Installation Backup &amp;amp; Restore   Usage  Basic commands Informative Actions  Confidential Transactions (Blind)   Wallet unlocking  With enhanced privacy Standard unlocking          Preview of Rhombus CLI  About Rhombus CLI Rhombus-cli offers all the essential features, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t include all the advanced bells and whistles of Rhombus graphical clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribute to Wiki</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/contribute/</guid>
      <description>List of incomplete articles How to contribute  Editing/creating pages   Useful Shortcodes  Table of Contents Buttons Images and video YouTube / Vimeo Icons Labels Hints Columns Tabs       List of incomplete articles Articles tagged with &amp;ldquo;TODO&amp;rdquo; are either completely missing or just unfinished. Since other articles are linking to them, these should be written ASAP. Contributing to these is highly appreciated!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
