<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>important on Rhombus Project Wiki</title>
    <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tags/important/</link>
    <description>Recent content in important on Rhombus Project Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://rhom.com/wiki/tags/important/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Transaction types</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/privacy/transaction-types/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/privacy/transaction-types/</guid>
      <description>As the highest privacy state requires the most transaction fee, it may not always be the best type of transaction depending on the situation, especially when privacy is not predominantly required by the user.
 Rhombus&amp;#39;s multiple privacy states      Public Blind Anon     Staking      Privacy ∗ ∗∗ ∗∗∗   Hidden TX amount      Anon TX participants      TX fees $ $$ $$$    Why has RHOM different privacy states?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to stake</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/overview/</guid>
      <description>Staking methods Comparison  Standalone staking Cold staking       To learn more in-depth about Rhombus&amp;rsquo;s Staking feature, read Rhombus Staking (intro).
Staking methods You can choose from few options on how to stake:
 Standalone – staking happens directly in your desktop wallet, your PC should be online ideally 24/7 (see below) Staking on a Pool – easily &amp;ldquo;pair&amp;rdquo; your desktop wallet with a Staking Pool; staking will happen automatically on pool Staking on dedicated staking device (DSD) – a fancy way to describe staking on your own SBC like Raspberry Pi or Rock64 without need to rely on third-party pool  Comparison     Standalone Staking pools Dedicated staking devices     Difficulty to setup easiest easy moderate   Staking happens directly in wallet on a pool on dedicated device   Staking type &amp;ldquo;hot&amp;rdquo; staking Cold Staking Cold Staking   Fees – 1–3 % –   Security lower high high   Howto guides – setup guide setup guide    Standalone staking is easiest and fastest way to start staking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securely storing Recovery Phrases</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/recovery-phrase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/recovery-phrase/</guid>
      <description>Recovery Phrases (sometimes also called Mnemonic or just Seed) are strings of usually 12, 18 or 24 words, which are used to recover crypto wallets in cases of emergency. That being said, whoever gets access to your Recovery Phrase can access your coins as well. This presents a security risk if your Recovery Phrase gets stolen or discovered by some malicious actor.
Finding the right balance Each security layer used to protect your Recovery Phrase (and optionally Recovery Passphrase) makes it harder for everyone to get access to your coins – that includes both attackers and yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wallets overview</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/wallets/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/wallets/overview/</guid>
      <description>You can use one or all of them, it&amp;rsquo;s up to you.
Overview Rhombus Core is a recommended wallet for most users as it offers the best of Rhombus&amp;rsquo;s features  Desktop Main, desktop wallets for Windows, macOS and Linux
 Rhombus Core – Qt-based wallet focused on stability and advanced features Rhombus Copay – Mobile &amp;amp; desktop wallet with multi-sig for increased security     Mobile Mobile wallets for Android and iOS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup &amp; Restore wallet</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/backup-restore-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/security/backup-restore-wallet/</guid>
      <description>Your funds are backed up by Recovery Phrase (~ mnemonic seed) during wallet creation and that is enough to keep your coins safe. However if you want to backup all the additional data like addresses saved in Address Book and more, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to backup your wallet.dat file.
Always backup your wallet.dat to a secure place (USB, external drive etc.) – if anyone would get access to it and knew your wallet password, they could steal your coins!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold staking setup</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/cold-staking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/tutorial/staking/cold-staking/</guid>
      <description>Before we dive into this guide, you might want to familiarize yourself with theory of cold staking, so that you know what we&amp;rsquo;re doing and why.
Rhombus&amp;rsquo;s cold staking setup is quite flexible, meaning there are many options how to stake – each approach has its pros and cons. This guide will outline all the possible variants, so that you can choose your own balance between convenience, privacy and security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Rhombus&#39;s PoS</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/staking/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/staking/intro/</guid>
      <description>About Rhombus Staking Passive Income Cold Staking  Cold Hardware Staking Quantum-resistance &amp;amp; Privacy       About Rhombus Staking Proof-of-Stake (PoS) is a type of algorithm by which a cryptocurrency blockchain network aims to achieve distributed consensus. In PoS-based cryptocurrencies, the creator of the next block is chosen via various combinations of random selection of wealth and age. In contrast, the algorithm of Proof-of-Work (PoW) based cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin rewards participants who solve complicated cryptographical puzzles in order to validate transactions and create new blocks (i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
