<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blockchain on Rhombus Project Wiki</title>
    <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blockchain on Rhombus Project Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Airdrop Details</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-airdrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-airdrop/</guid>
      <description>Airdrop Rhombus coin initial distrubution includes 6 billion RHOM distrubted at a ratio of 500:1 to all BTC addresses with a positive bitcoin balance over 0.001 before BTC block 660023. They are claimable by signing a message from your bitcoin address and submitting to Rhom AirDrop before December 5th, 2021.
 Airdrop API Airdrop Details How To Claim Your Airdrop How To Sign a Message For RHOM  Currently Ongoing Until December 5th, 2021  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICO Detials</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-ico/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-ico/</guid>
      <description>ICO Details Round one currently under until DATE HERE  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Bitcoin codebase</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/bitcoin-codebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/bitcoin-codebase/</guid>
      <description>RHOM is hosted by its own blockchain and is not a token built on another chain (i.e. ERC-20 tokens).
Advantages Being built on the latest Bitcoin codebase not only allows the Rhombus platform to benefit from both Bitcoin’s stability and security, but also enables developers to leverage and easily fork any product, service and technology development from the Bitcoin developer community.
Recent Bitcoin developments implemented in Rhombus include but are not limited to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scalability</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/blockchain-scalability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/blockchain-scalability/</guid>
      <description>Native Segregated Witness (Segwit) Bulletproofs Lightning Network  Instant Payments Scalability Low Cost Cross-Chain       Native Segregated Witness (Segwit) The Rhombus platform was deployed with a native implementation of Segwit.
This has the added benefit of making all transactions (including private ones) go through Segwit by default, resulting in better scalability and cheaper transaction fees.
Unlike forked Segwit implementations, 100% of Rhombus addresses are compatible with Segregated Witness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specifications</title>
      <link>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhom.com/wiki/learn/blockchain/rhombus-specifications/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain          Codebase Always up-to-date with latest Bitcoin Core   Consensus mechanism Rhombus Proof-of-Stake (RPoS)   Block time 150 seconds (Quicker then BTC)   Block size 2 MB (2× larger than BTC)    Coin supply          Total &amp;amp; circulating supply between 1-11 billion RHOM (check link for exact number)   ICO Disptrubtion max 200 Million RHOM   Airdrop Distrubution max 10 billion RHOM    Staking          Block reward 100 RHOM   Coin maturity 192 confirmations (~8 hours)   Yearly interest rate 0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
